

AZIZBEK BALTAEV

Full-Stack Developer

Personal Profile

I am an experienced full-stack developer interested in projects that require both back-end and front-end experience. My passion lies in learning about the latest technologies.

Technical Skills

ReactJS, Redux, Thunk
JavaScript, Jest
NodeJS, ExpressJS, Firebase,
MongoDB, Mongoose
Git, GitHub, Heroku
HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap

Contact Information

Phone: +7 (904) 551 81 01
Email: bazizbek@gmail.com
LinkedIn: <u>@azizbek_baltaev</u>
GitHub: <u>https://github.com/BAzizbek</u>

Short-Term Goals

- Learn TypeScript
- Take part in Hackathon
- Read 1 technical book
- Keep fit
- Maintain knowledge of developing technologies

Character References

Katrin Alimova

Chief Technology Officer | Elbrus Coding Bootcamp alimova.katrin8@gmail.com

Yuriy Pliskovsky

Senior Full-Stack Developer zzaafamania@gmail.com

Relative Work Experience

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Freelance | Worldwide | 2020 - present

- Participated in code reviews with development teams
- Developed website components using modern frameworks
- Collaborated with designers and other developers to launch web applications
- Optimised home and landing pages
- Collaborated with back-end developers and UX designers
- Designed websites, from layout to function, according to client specifications
- Client application development using: React, Redux, Thunk.

Certificates

ELBRUS CODING BOOTCAMP Full-Stack Developer | 2021

- MERN stack intensive course
- 500 hundred hours offline-course

FRECODECAMP.ORG Full-Stack Developer | 2020

- Responsive Web Design Certification
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification
- Front End Development Libraries Certification
- APIs and Microservices Certification

Academic Background

SAINT-PETERSBURG STATE UNIVERSITY OF CIVIL AVIATION Management | 2019

- Grade 4/5
- Accomplished bachelor's degree with concentration in human resources

URGENCH STATE COLLEGE OF HOUSEHOLD SERVICES Information Technologies | 2012

- Grade 5/5
- Studied basics of computer science
- Winner 3 consecutive competitions in mathematics

Past Work Experience

HR SPECIALIST

Urgench International Airport | Uzbekistan | 2019 - 2020

HR TRAINEE

Ceterer Staffing Agency | UK | June 2018 - Oct 2018

HR INTERN

Elitch Gardens | USA | May 2017 - Oct 2017